Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1920 -- 1999; 1985 -- 1996; MS074.002; 38.4 Linear Feet
  - Mabon, Lon, 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.050.00027 (Box 50)
  - Mabry, John R., 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.050.00028 (Box 50)
  - MacPherson, Pauline, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.050.00029 (Box 50)
  - Madera Ed. Support Assn., 1992; MS074.002.050.00030 (Box 50)
  - Madison Project, 1996; MS074.002.050.00031 (Box 50)
  - Madonna, Kevin, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.050.00032 (Box 50)
    Environmentalism and Christianity
  - Magnuson, Roger J., 1987; MS074.002.050.00033 (Box 50)
  - Maher, Bishop Leo T., 1990; MS074.002.050.00034 (Box 50)
  - ME - Maine, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00035 (Box 50)
  - Mainstream Coalition, 1994; MS074.002.050.00036 (Box 50)
  - Mainstream Voter's Project, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.050.00037 (Box 50)
  - Mamantov, Tanya, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.050.00038 (Box 50)
    Sue Kelly, gun control
  - Manifest Sons of God, MS074.002.050.00039 (Box 50)
  - Mainstream Voters Project, 1996; MS074.002.050.00040 (Box 50)
  - Manson, Chas., 1986; MS074.002.050.00041 (Box 50)
  - Manuel, Kathryn C., 1986; MS074.002.050.00042 (Box 50)
  - Mapplethorpe, 1990; MS074.002.050.00043 (Box 50)
  - Maranatha Ministries, 1985; MS074.002.050.00044 (Box 50)
  - March for Jesus, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00045 (Box 50)
  - Marian Fathers, 1995; MS074.002.050.00046 (Box 50)
  - Marriage, MS074.002.050.00047 (Box 50)
  - Marrs, Texe, 1990; MS074.002.050.00048 (Box 50)
  - Marsh, Dave, 1991; MS074.002.050.00049 (Box 50)
  - Marsh, Eric, 1992; MS074.002.050.00050 (Box 50)
  - Marshall, Peter, 1996; MS074.002.050.00051 (Box 50)
  - Martin, Dave, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.050.00052 (Box 50)
  - Mary, 1984 -- 1991; MS074.002.050.00053 (Box 50)
  - Mary Knoll Fathers, 1986; MS074.002.050.00054 (Box 50)
  - MD - Maryland, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.050.00055 (Box 50)
  - Masons, 1993; MS074.002.050.00056 (Box 50)
  - Massachusetts MA, 1993 -- 1997; MS074.002.050.00057 (Box 50)
  - Mass Citizens for Life, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00058 (Box 50)
  - MA Con Con, 1983 -- 1987; MS074.002.050.00059 (Box 50)
  - Mass. Family Institute, 1994; MS074.002.050.00060 (Box 50)
  - MA referenda, 1986; MS074.002.050.00061 (Box 50)
  - MGLPC Mass. Gay - Lesbian Political Caucus, 1995; MS074.002.050.00062 (Box 50)
  - MA - RR Hotspots, 1907 -- 1993; MS074.002.050.00063 (Box 50)
  - MA - State Legislature calendars, 1986 -- 1987; MS074.002.050.00064 (Box 50)
  - Mass - Newton, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.050.00065 (Box 50)
  - Massachusetts - non-profits, 1995; MS074.002.050.00066 (Box 50)
  - Massachusetts - school boards, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.050.00067 (Box 50)
  - Mass. Stand, 1995; MS074.002.050.00068 (Box 50)
  - Massachusetts Republicans, 1985 -- 1986; MS074.002.050.00069 (Box 50)
  - The Match, Fred Woodworth, 1992; MS074.002.050.00070 (Box 50)
  - Mawyer, Martin, 1984 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00071 (Box 50)
  - McCarthyism, 1952 -- 1986; MS074.002.050.00072 (Box 50)
  - McAllister, Dawson, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00073 (Box 50)
    Includes materials from Betty McCollister
  - McCormack, Rev. Billy, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.050.00074 (Box 50)
  - McCormick, Michael (PA - 20th Congress District), 1994; MS074.002.050.00075 (Box 50)
  - McDowell, Jeanne, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.050.00076 (Box 50)
  - McGregor, Mona, 1992; MS074.002.050.00077 (Box 50)
  - McKeever Strategy Letter, 1986; MS074.002.050.00078 (Box 50)
  - McKown, Delos B., 1986 -- 1991; MS074.002.050.00079 (Box 50)
  - McNamee, Lawrence and Brian, 1988; MS074.002.050.00080 (Box 50)
  - McPehrson, Aimee Semple, 1930 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00081 (Box 50)
  - McVeigh, Timothy, 1995; MS074.002.050.00082 (Box 50)
  - Mecham, Evan, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.050.00083 (Box 50)
  - Media Bypass, 1995; MS074.002.050.00084 (Box 50)
  - Media Coalition, 1988 -- 1994; MS074.002.050.00085 (Box 50)
  - Medical care, 1994; MS074.002.050.00086 (Box 50)
  - Medved, Michael, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.050.00087 (Box 50)
  - Meese, Edwin, 1987; MS074.002.050.00088 (Box 50)
  - Meese Commission on Porno, 1986; MS074.002.050.00089 (Box 50)
  - Membership renewal form, MS074.002.050.00090 (Box 50)
  - Meneilly Sermon, 1993; MS074.002.050.00091 (Box 50)
  - Menorah Ministry, 1996; MS074.002.050.00092 (Box 50)
  - Mennonites, 1993; MS074.002.050.00093 (Box 50)
  - Mergens, Bible clubs, 1990; MS074.002.050.00094 (Box 50)
  - Mertens, Ilse, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.050.00095 (Box 50)
  - MESA (Madera Educational Support Assoc.), 1991; MS074.002.050.00096 (Box 50)
  - Messianic Jews, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.050.00097 (Box 50)
  - Messiah's Mandate, 1992; MS074.002.050.00098 (Box 50)
  - Mort Metersky, 1996; MS074.002.050.00099 (Box 50)
  - Metzgers, 1992; MS074.002.050.00100 (Box 50)
  - Michas, Peter A., 1989; MS074.002.050.00101 (Box 50)
  - Michefelder, Joseph, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00102 (Box 50)
  - Michigan MI (Michigan), 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.050.00103 (Box 50)
  - Mid-East, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.050.00104 (Box 50)
  - Midnight Call Ministry, MS074.002.050.00105 (Box 50)
  - Miles, Austin [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - Miles, Austin [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.051.00002 (Box 51)
  - Miles, Austin, MS074.002.051.00003 (Box 51)
  - Militias - from Internet 12/95 [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00004 (Box 51)
  - Militias - from Internet 12/95 [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00005 (Box 51)
  - Militias [1 of 3], 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00006 (Box 51)
  - Militias [2 of 3], 1995; MS074.002.051.00007 (Box 51)
  - Militias [3 of 3], 1994; MS074.002.051.00008 (Box 51)
  - Militia - Montana, 1996; MS074.002.051.00009 (Box 51)
  - Militia (New Hamp.), 1996; MS074.002.051.00010 (Box 51)
  - Militia / PRA / Berlet, 1995; MS074.002.051.00011 (Box 51)
  - Millenialists, 1984 -- 1992; MS074.002.051.00012 (Box 51)
  - Bill Miller - Duncanville, TX, 1991 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00013 (Box 51)
    Audiocassette titled "Edward Parker 2/23/90 Duncanville, TX" removed to audiocasette area of collection
  - Military, 1994; MS074.002.051.00014 (Box 51)
  - Ministries - small misc., 1989 -- 1994; MS074.002.051.00015 (Box 51)
  - Ministries - small, miscellaneous, 1987 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00016 (Box 51)
  - Minichello, Steve, 1994; MS074.002.051.00017 (Box 51)
  - MN (Minnesota), 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00018 (Box 51)
  - MS (Mississippi), 1994 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00019 (Box 51)
  - Mission Aviation Fellowship, 1992; MS074.002.051.00020 (Box 51)
  - Missionaries, 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.051.00021 (Box 51)
  - Missionaries to the preborn, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.051.00022 (Box 51)
  - Missouri, 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00023 (Box 51)
  - Moms in Touch, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.051.00024 (Box 51)
  - MT (Montana), 1992 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00025 (Box 51)
  - Monteith, Stanley, M.D., 1991; MS074.002.051.00026 (Box 51)
  - Moody Bible Institute, 1991 -- 1994; MS074.002.051.00027 (Box 51)
  - Moon, Rev. (Moonies), 1983 -- 1993; MS074.002.051.00028 (Box 51)
  - Moore, Genie, 1991; MS074.002.051.00029 (Box 51)
  - Moral Majority, 1983 -- 1989; MS074.002.051.00030 (Box 51)
  - Morality in Media, 1985 -- 1989; MS074.002.051.00031 (Box 51)
  - Morecraft, Joe III, 1995; MS074.002.051.00032 (Box 51)
  - Mormons, 1975 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00033 (Box 51)
  - Morris, Philip, 1992; MS074.002.051.00034 (Box 51)
  - Morse, John W., 1995; MS074.002.051.00035 (Box 51)
  - Mother Jones, 1994; MS074.002.051.00036 (Box 51)
  - Moyers, Bill, 1986 -- 1987; MS074.002.051.00037 (Box 51)
  - Movies, 1986 -- 1990; MS074.002.051.00038 (Box 51)
  - Muhammad, Khalid Abdul, MS074.002.051.00039 (Box 51)
  - Multiculturalism, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00040 (Box 51)
  - Mumford, Bob, 1990; MS074.002.051.00041 (Box 51)
    Life Changers
  - Murray, Wm. J. evangelist, 1993; MS074.002.051.00042 (Box 51)
  - Music business (also record labels), 1990; MS074.002.051.00043 (Box 51)
  - Music censorship, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.051.00044 (Box 51)
  - Music in Action, 1988; MS074.002.051.00045 (Box 51)
  - Muslims, 1992; MS074.002.051.00046 (Box 51)
  - NAAWP, 1996; MS074.002.051.00047 (Box 51)
    National Association for the Advancement of White People
  - NARAL, 1989; MS074.002.051.00048 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Assoc. of Christian Educators / Citizens for Excellence in Education, 1995; MS074.002.051.00049 (Box 51)
  - NBC News, MS074.002.051.00050 (Box 51)
  - The Nation, 1985; MS074.002.051.00051 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Assoc. Artists Organizations (NAAO), 1992; MS074.002.051.00052 (Box 51)
  - NACE/CEE, Nat'l Assoc. for Christian Educators, 1996; MS074.002.051.00053 (Box 51)
  - N.A.R.S.C., 1987; MS074.002.051.00054 (Box 51)
  - National Association Evangelicals, 1987 -- 1993; MS074.002.051.00055 (Box 51)
    National Association of Evangelicals
  - National Campaign, 1992; MS074.002.051.00056 (Box 51)
    National Campiagn for Freedom of Expression
  - Nat'l Campaign for Freedom of Expression, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00057 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Center for Science Education [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00058 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Center for Science Education [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00059 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Christian Voter Moblization Campaign, 1996; MS074.002.051.00060 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l. Citizens Action Network, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.002.051.00061 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Coal. Ag. Censorship, 1991 -- 1995; MS074.002.051.00062 (Box 51)
    National Association Against Censorship
  - Nat'l Coalition Against Censorship [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00063 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Coalition Against Censorship [2 of 2], 1984 -- 1994; MS074.002.051.00064 (Box 51)
  - National Coalition Against Porno, 1987 -- 1989; MS074.002.051.00065 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Conference of Christians and Jews, 1994; MS074.002.051.00066 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Day of Prayer, 1992 -- 1996; MS074.002.051.00067 (Box 51)
  - Nat'l Emergency Civil Liberties Committee [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Emergency Civil Liberties Committee [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1987; MS074.002.052.00002 (Box 52)
  - National Empowerment Television, 1991 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00003 (Box 52)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1989 -- 1993; MS074.002.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - National Education Assoc., 1986 -- 1991; MS074.002.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l. Family Legal Foundation, 1990 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00006 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Gay/Lesbian Task Force, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00007 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Gay/Lesbian Task Force manuscript, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l. Institute of Family & Life Advocates, 1994; MS074.002.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Institute of Womanhood, 1993; MS074.002.052.00010 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Interfaith Cable Coalition Inc., 1994; MS074.002.052.00011 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l & International Religion Report, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00012 (Box 52)
  - NJDC Nat'l Jewish Democratic Council, 1996; MS074.002.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - National Lawyer's Guild, 1989; MS074.002.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l League for Sep. of Church / State, 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.052.00015 (Box 52)
  - National League for Sep. of Church, 1988 -- 1990; MS074.002.052.00016 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Legal Foundation, 1987 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00017 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Network of Grantmakers, 1993; MS074.002.052.00018 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l. Parents Commission, 1994; MS074.002.052.00019 (Box 52)
  - National Parks, Christian ministry, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00020 (Box 52)
  - National Public Radio, 1984; MS074.002.052.00021 (Box 52)
  - NRB National Religious Broadcasters [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00022 (Box 52)
  - NRB National Religious Broadcasters [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00023 (Box 52)
  - National Rifle Association (NRA), 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00024 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Right to Life, 1986 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00025 (Box 52)
  - National School Boards Assoc., 1993; MS074.002.052.00026 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Women's Political Caucus, 1993; MS074.002.052.00027 (Box 52)
  - Nat'l Writers Union, 1993; MS074.002.052.00028 (Box 52)
  - Native Americans, 1987 -- 1992; MS074.002.052.00029 (Box 52)
  - Naturist Action Com., 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.052.00030 (Box 52)
  - Naturist Society [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1996; MS074.002.052.00031 (Box 52)
  - Naturist Society [2 of 2], 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00032 (Box 52)
  - The Navigators, Discipleship Journal, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00033 (Box 52)
  - Nazi war crimes criminals, 1988 -- 1989; MS074.002.052.00034 (Box 52)
  - Nazis - rise to power, 1986 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00035 (Box 52)
  - Nebraska, 1994; MS074.002.052.00036 (Box 52)
  - Nebraska - schools, politics, MS074.002.052.00037 (Box 52)
  - Neighbors Network, 1994; MS074.002.052.00038 (Box 52)
  - Neo-Nazi's, 1986 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00039 (Box 52)
  - Kennedy's letter to Nerken, 1984; MS074.002.052.00040 (Box 52)
  - NET, 1995; MS074.002.052.00041 (Box 52)
  - NV - Nevada, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00042 (Box 52)
  - Nevada Freedom Coalition, 1996; MS074.002.052.00043 (Box 52)
  - Nevel Ministries, 1993; MS074.002.052.00044 (Box 52)
  - New Age, 1986 -- 1990; MS074.002.052.00045 (Box 52)
  - NH - New Hampshire, 1994; MS074.002.052.00046 (Box 52)
  - New Era Foundation, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.052.00047 (Box 52)
  - N.H., Merrimack, 1996; MS074.002.052.00048 (Box 52)
  - NIF - New Israel Fund, 1990; MS074.002.052.00049 (Box 52)
  - NJ - New Jersey, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00050 (Box 52)
  - NM - New Mexico, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00051 (Box 52)
  - New Music Seminar, 1988; MS074.002.052.00052 (Box 52)
  - N. Orleans Leaders Congress, 1986; MS074.002.052.00053 (Box 52)
  - New Missions, MS074.002.052.00054 (Box 52)
  - New Party, 1992; MS074.002.052.00055 (Box 52)
  - Newsday, 1990; MS074.002.052.00056 (Box 52)
  - Newsletter on Intellectual Freedom, 1987 -- 1992; MS074.002.052.00057 (Box 52)
  - Newsletter Services, Inc., 1990; MS074.002.052.00058 (Box 52)
  - New Sound, Inc., 1995; MS074.002.052.00059 (Box 52)
  - New Square, 1994; MS074.002.052.00060 (Box 52)
  - New York legislation - activism, court decisions, 1993; MS074.002.052.00061 (Box 52)
  - Militia / biosphere N.Y., 1995; MS074.002.052.00062 (Box 52)
  - NY New York, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00063 (Box 52)
  - New York State - Buffalo, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.052.00064 (Box 52)
  - New York State School Superintendents, 1994; MS074.002.052.00065 (Box 52)
  - NY State United Teachers, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.052.00066 (Box 52)
  - New York Times (Kenneth Briggs), 1986; MS074.002.052.00067 (Box 52)
  - NY Foundation for the Arts, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.052.00068 (Box 52)
  - New Yorkers for Constitutional Freedoms, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00069 (Box 52)
  - NY Schools, 1996; MS074.002.052.00070 (Box 52)
  - NY Charter Schools, 1998 -- 1999; MS074.002.052.00071 (Box 52)
  - New Yorkers for Constitutional Freedom, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.052.00072 (Box 52)
  - New Yorkers for constutional freedoms, 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - New Yorkers family research foundation, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00002 (Box 53)
  - News watch, 1992; MS074.002.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - New world order, 1990 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Nicaragua, 1985; MS074.002.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Suzannn Nichole, 1990; MS074.002.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - Ralph Nielsen, 1992; MS074.002.053.00007 (Box 53)
  - Niemoeller, Martin, 1992; MS074.002.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - Nirenberg, Charles/dairy mart, 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - Noah's Ark, 1989 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00010 (Box 53)
  - Noble, Kerry, 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - Noebel, Rev. David A., 1974 -- 1983; MS074.002.053.00012 (Box 53)
  - Nonprofits, 1995; MS074.002.053.00013 (Box 53)
  - Nora Lam ministries, MS074.002.053.00014 (Box 53)
  - North American congress/evangelization, 1986 -- 1987; MS074.002.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - North Carolina, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - North Dakota, 1994; MS074.002.053.00017 (Box 53)
  - North Carolina civil liberties union, 1990; MS074.002.053.00018 (Box 53)
  - North, Gary-remnant review, 1985 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00019 (Box 53)
  - North, Oliver (lt. col.), 1986 -- 1996; MS074.002.053.00020 (Box 53)
  - North, Oliver, 1988 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00021 (Box 53)
  - Northampton for Traditional Values, 1995; MS074.002.053.00022 (Box 53)
  - Northeast Atheist Assoc., 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00023 (Box 53)
  - NOW-Nat'l. Org. for Women, 1992; MS074.002.053.00024 (Box 53)
  - NSWAP (National Socialist White America Party), 1993; MS074.002.053.00025 (Box 53)
  - NOW, 1985 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00026 (Box 53)
  - Nudity, 1994; MS074.002.053.00027 (Box 53)
  - OBE, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00028 (Box 53)
  - Obits, 1987 -- 1990; MS074.002.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - Occupational Christianity, 1993; MS074.002.053.00030 (Box 53)
  - Odyssey, outcome based education, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00031 (Box 53)
  - O'Hair, Madalyn, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00032 (Box 53)
  - Of The People, 1993; MS074.002.053.00033 (Box 53)
  - Ohio, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00034 (Box 53)
  - Oklahoma, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00035 (Box 53)
  - Oklahoma, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00036 (Box 53)
  - Oklahoma City, 1995; MS074.002.053.00037 (Box 53)
  - Militias-loose materials, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00038 (Box 53)
  - Oklahoma Observer, 1993; MS074.002.053.00039 (Box 53)
  - OLE, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.002.053.00040 (Box 53)
  - Olver, John, 1995; MS074.002.053.00041 (Box 53)
  - Omega letter, 1991 -- 1992; MS074.002.053.00042 (Box 53)
  - One Nation Under God, 1991; MS074.002.053.00043 (Box 53)
  - One World Government, 1987; MS074.002.053.00044 (Box 53)
  - Op Ed, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.053.00045 (Box 53)
  - Onward Christian Soldiers, related materials, 1996; MS074.002.053.00046 (Box 53)
  - Onward Christian Soldiers, 1996; MS074.002.053.00047 (Box 53)
  - Op Ed, 1985 -- 1988; MS074.002.053.00048 (Box 53)
  - Open Doors with Brother Andrew, 1990; MS074.002.053.00049 (Box 53)
  - Open Enterprises, 1991; MS074.002.053.00050 (Box 53)
  - Operation Blessing, MS074.002.053.00051 (Box 53)
  - Operation Rescue, 1989 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00052 (Box 53)
  - Operation Rescue, Randall Terry, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00053 (Box 53)
  - Operation Rescue Calif. donor list, 1994; MS074.002.053.00054 (Box 53)
  - OR fact sheet, 1993; MS074.002.053.00055 (Box 53)
  - Opus Dei, 1981 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00056 (Box 53)
  - Osteen, John, 1988 -- 1990; MS074.002.053.00057 (Box 53)
  - O'Sullivan, Gerry, 1994; MS074.002.053.00058 (Box 53)
  - Ottingen Foundation, 1992; MS074.002.053.00059 (Box 53)
  - Otis, George, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.053.00060 (Box 53)
  - Our Father's House, 1993; MS074.002.053.00061 (Box 53)
  - Outcome Based Education, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00062 (Box 53)
  - Oregon, 1990 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00063 (Box 53)
  - Oregon Citizens Alliance, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00064 (Box 53)
  - Oregon Citizens Alliance, 1987 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00065 (Box 53)
  - Oregon/white supremacist, 1995; MS074.002.053.00066 (Box 53)
  - Oregon Coalition for Free Expression, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00067 (Box 53)
  - Oregon-Right To Life, 1995; MS074.002.053.00068 (Box 53)
  - Packwood, Bob, MS074.002.053.00069 (Box 53)
  - PACs, 1985; MS074.002.053.00070 (Box 53)
  - Pagan Educational Network, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.002.053.00071 (Box 53)
  - Paganism, 1993; MS074.002.053.00072 (Box 53)
  - Paladin Legal Defense Fund, 1996; MS074.002.053.00073 (Box 53)
  - Palau, Luis, 1986; MS074.002.053.00074 (Box 53)
  - Panoch, 1988; MS074.002.053.00075 (Box 53)
  - Parents for Educational Choice, 1993; MS074.002.053.00076 (Box 53)
  - Parents' Music Resource Center, 1985 -- 1991; MS074.002.053.00077 (Box 53)
  - Parents Advocating Great Education, P.A.G.E., 1995; MS074.002.053.00078 (Box 53)
  - Parents' Rights, 1993; MS074.002.053.00079 (Box 53)
  - Park, Charles, 1993; MS074.002.053.00080 (Box 53)
  - Loren E. Parks, MS074.002.053.00081 (Box 53)
  - Parochiaid, 1985 -- 1993; MS074.002.053.00082 (Box 53)
  - Parochiaid, Massachusetts, 1985 -- 1986; MS074.002.053.00083 (Box 53)
  - Pastor's Weekly Briefing [1 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; MS074.002.053.00084 (Box 53)
  - Pastor's Weekly Briefing [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.053.00085 (Box 53)
  - Patriotism, MS074.002.053.00086 (Box 53)
  - Paul, Congressman Ron, 1993; MS074.002.053.00087 (Box 53)
  - PAW, 1995; MS074.002.053.00088 (Box 53)
  - Peacocke, Dennis, 1992; MS074.002.053.00089 (Box 53)
  - Norman Vincent Peale, 1985 -- 1987; MS074.002.053.00090 (Box 53)
  - Pearl, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania [1of 2], 1993 -- 1996; MS074.002.054.00002 (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1996; MS074.002.054.00003 (Box 54)
  - Pennsylvania Family Institute, 1990; MS074.002.054.00004 (Box 54)
  - Pentecostals, 1988 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00005 (Box 54)
  - People for the American Way, 1996; MS074.002.054.00006 (Box 54)
  - P Flag, 1996; MS074.002.054.00007 (Box 54)
  - Pharr, Suzanne, 1994; MS074.002.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - Phelps, Fred, 1994; MS074.002.054.00009 (Box 54)
  - Phyllis Schafly Report, 1982 -- 1994; MS074.002.054.00010 (Box 54)
  - Pilgrim Family Institute, 1993; MS074.002.054.00011 (Box 54)
  - Pioneer Clubs, MS074.002.054.00012 (Box 54)
  - Pinder, Gary, R., 1986 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00013 (Box 54)
  - PPFA Insider, 1993; MS074.002.054.00014 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood-Opposition Project, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00015 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parnethood-manual, MS074.002.054.00016 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood, Central Arizona, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.054.00017 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1994; MS074.002.054.00018 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood of N.E. Texas, 1994; MS074.002.054.00019 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood of No. New England, 1995; MS074.002.054.00020 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood, Rochester and Genesee Valley, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.002.054.00021 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood of SE PA, 1994; MS074.002.054.00022 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood, Upper Hudson, 1993; MS074.002.054.00023 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood of Wisc., 1990 -- 1993; MS074.002.054.00024 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood of Omaha-Council Bluffs, 1994; MS074.002.054.00025 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood-attacks on, 1994; MS074.002.054.00026 (Box 54)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1994 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00027 (Box 54)
  - Playboy-public relations, MS074.002.054.00028 (Box 54)
  - Playboy, 1984 -- 1991; MS074.002.054.00029 (Box 54)
  - Charles Pluckhahn, 1994; MS074.002.054.00030 (Box 54)
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00031 (Box 54)
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1992; MS074.002.054.00032 (Box 54)
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1991; MS074.002.054.00033 (Box 54)
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1991; MS074.002.054.00034 (Box 54)
  - Podesta Assoc., 1994; MS074.002.054.00035 (Box 54)
  - Polack, Phyllis, 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.054.00036 (Box 54)
  - Political Research Association, 1981 -- 1994; MS074.002.054.00037 (Box 54)
  - Political Research Associates, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00038 (Box 54)
  - Political Research Associates, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.002.054.00039 (Box 54)
  - Politics of Culture, 1992; MS074.002.054.00040 (Box 54)
  - Pollard, Jonathan, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.002.054.00041 (Box 54)
  - Polls, 1992; MS074.002.054.00042 (Box 54)
  - Pontier, Raymond J., 1987 -- 1988; MS074.002.054.00043 (Box 54)
  - Pope John Paul II Park, 1988; MS074.002.054.00044 (Box 54)
  - Pope and Jesus, MS074.002.054.00045 (Box 54)
  - Populists, 1995; MS074.002.054.00046 (Box 54)
  - Pornography, 1986 -- 1993; MS074.002.054.00047 (Box 54)
  - Pornography, 1985 -- 1993; MS074.002.054.00048 (Box 54)